♪ Street lights fade into the haze ♪
♪ We don't care what the world says ♪
♪ Quiet like a secret we keep ♪
♪ Close enough to feel your breathe ♪
♪ Rules are made to fall apart  ♪
♪ When you hold me in the dark ♪
♪ Every second feels so wrong ♪
♪ But it's where I belong ♪
♪ We shouldn't stay, but we don't leave ♪
♪ This quiet chemistry ♪
♪ Soft and slow, we cross the line ♪
♪ Just one more time ♪
♪ Slow embrace in the silent dark ♪
♪ Forbidden but it feels so right ♪
Not enough.
Not enough?
This is already
the most formal style in this store.
Not flashy enough.
You're going to a board meeting,
not walking the red carpet.
It's good enough.
The onboarding meeting
in front of those old guys
is my red carpet.
I have to make them remember
that I am back.
[Dearest: Episode 19]
In that case,
why not try this one?
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
The dress fits perfectly
and suits you well.
It's just that...
something is missing.
Add them,
and now it's perfect.
I'll take the dress.
Wrap it up.
Okay, Mrs. Yin.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Wen.
She is
our top-tier VIP,
so she has priority to purchase all items.
So...
So now,
are you treating me as a fitting model?
Doesn't it look pretty good?
Any clothes,
as long as I wear them,
only belong to me.
Mrs. Yin, thank you for your help.
We are already engaged.
You are welcome to attend our wedding.
Mr. Jiang seems to have misunderstood,
or rather, is too narcissistic.
Don't worry.
I have no interest in you.
Pay by card.
The dress suits you well.
It's yours.
Who is she?
The daughter of the State Councilor.
Now she's a senior envoy
at the Presidential Office.
She was the one who saved me
at the abandoned factory before.
It seems that
she is coming for me.
But you can only be mine.
On such an important day,
you're still replying to emails here.
Can't you leave them until tomorrow?
This cross-border email today
must be sent out tonight.
Then at least
take a five-minute break first.
Cedarwood?
Isn't it
the custom scent
you picked to set the mood
for your distinguished guests?
Cloudsea's service motto
is to make customers forget worldly cares.
Since you are so distracted,
it's our fault.
It seems you need some
personalized services.
You are very good at
using own advantages
to interrupt the key figure's work.
Emails won't run away
but I will.
Boss, here is an encrypted document...
An encrypted document
that needs your signature.
No problem. Tell them to be selective
about their people.
Okay,
I'll step out now.
Jiang Yu...
You...
Are you still in the mood to read emails?
Your service tonight
is just about passable.
Passable?
Then let me show you
what it means
to be blinded by lust.